<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<!--
	Junk/Misc Items
-->

<string_table>
	
	<string id="st_porn">
		<text>Russian PLAYBOY</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_porn_descr">
		<text>100-pages worth of prime nude Russian girls. Probably the best way to travel to a better place, at least mentally. Westerners often joke about it saying "From Russia with love".\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] weapon cleaning and lubrication (+2%)</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_survivalguide">
		<text>Ukrainian Special Forces Survival Guide</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_survivalguide_descr">
		<text>You have studied this survival guide many times before. For this reason, it does not have any educational value, but you should be able to sell it for some quick cash. Some stalkers may want to take a look at it.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] weapon cleaning and lubrication (+3%)</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_guitar_name">
		<text>Guitar</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_guitar_descr">
		<text>Guitar is a string instrument widely used by stalkers of all factions throughout the Zone in order to raise spirits and fraternize. Stalkers can often be seen playing the guitar in camps, outposts or other places of relative safety - usually by the fire. \n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_harmonica_name">
		<text>Harmonica</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_harmonica_descr">
		<text>For blues and prison romance lovers.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_steel_wool">
		<text>Steel wool</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_steel_wool_descr">
		<text>Steel wool, also known as wire wool or wire sponge, is a bundle of strands of very fine soft steel filaments. It is used as an abrasive in finishing and repair work for polishing wood or metal objects, cleaning household cookware, and sanding in light painting. Steel wool is made from low-carbon steel (carbon content is low enough to be close to plain iron). It is not made by drawing "steel wool wire" through a tapered die, but rather by a process more like broaching where a heavy steel wire is pulled through a toothed die that removes a thin wire shaving. Bundles of steel wool can be used in precision equipment cleaning and to improve spreading of lubricants and cleaning solvents.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] technological item\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+6%)</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_grease">
		<text>Industrial grease</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grease_descr">
		<text>Grease is a semisolid lubricant. It generally consists of a soap emulsified with mineral or vegetable oil. Greases are applied to mechanisms that cannot be lubricated constantly or where typical lubricating oil would not stay in position. They also act as sealants to prevent ingress of water and incompressible materials. Grease-lubricated bearings have greater frictional characteristics due to their high viscosity.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] technological item\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] high quality\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+6%)</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_roubles">
		<text>Old coins</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_roubles_descr">
		<text>Trade in the Zone is conducted mainly by means of electronic transactions for safety and managing reasons. But many stalkers keep at least a few coins in their pockets in case they want to buy smaller things like cigarettes. This makes life easier and conserves battery life.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_shovel_old">
		<text>Metal shovel</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_shovel_old_descr">
		<text>An old metal shovel used for various field purposes. Few people actually keep shovels in their backpacks as they are quite commonly found in the Zone, especially in industrial areas.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_shovel_mili">
		<text>Military field shovel</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_shovel_mili_descr">
		<text>High-quality black military shovel. Used for numerous field purposes. Training regimen of Spetsnaz soldiers covers hand-to-hand combat and use of hand-held weapons and other equipment for the purposes of eliminating enemies. One famous example is the entrenching shovel which is a formidable weapon in close combat when used by a Spetsnaz operator.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] military item</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_meinkampf">
		<text>Mein Kampf</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_meinkampf_descr">
		<text>Adolf Hitler's strategic memoires collected in a single book. The book and all that it stands for are hated by many, which makes this an item of high symbolic value. Adolf Hitler (20 April 1889 - 30 April 1945) was an Austrian-born German politician and the leader of the National Socialist German Workers Party (German: Nationalsozialistische Deutsche Arbeiterpartei (NSDAP), commonly referred to as the Nazi Party). He was chancellor of Germany from 1933 to 1945 and dictator of Nazi Germany (as Fuhrer und Reichskanzler) from 1934 to 1945. Hitler is responsible for the founding of Nazism, the start of World War II, and the Holocaust.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] personal belongings\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+2%)</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_journal">
		<text>Personal journal</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_journal_descr">
		<text>Personal journal with a number of primitive maps and notations. In a leather binding. Simple survival tips for the common man and nothing of much value.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] personal belongings\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+2%)</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_maps_kit">
		<text>Mapmaking kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_maps_kit_descr">
		<text>Mapmaking kit containing a set of pens and measurement instruments. All in a waterproof and camouflaged cover of high quality. Used by and issued to Ukrainian artillery personnel. Some maps have not yet been completed. Your PDA is much more useful than any of this.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] technological item\n
		%c[0,204,0,51] • %c[0,140,140,140] unusable</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_welding_goggles">
		<text>Welding goggles</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_welding_goggles_descr">
		<text>Old and corroded welding goggles with a broken leather band. Welding goggles are designed to provide eye protection while welding or cutting. Useless in their current state and of no to little value.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_survival_kit">
		<text>Small survival kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_survival_kit_descr">
		<text>Survival kit containing fabric, sewing needles and a few leather strips. Primarily used as a means to stop the bleeding and treat lacerations, in the hands of a skilled user this small survival kit may prove essential during prolonged excursions in the Zone. It can also be utilized for outfit repairs of even most severe damage.\n \n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] high quality\n
		%c[0,204,0,51] • %c[0,140,140,140] slow usage (field kit)\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] immediately stops heavy bleeding\n
		%c[0,204,0,51] • %c[0,140,140,140] prolonged body recovery time\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] outfit repairs (+7%)</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_jewelry_box">
		<text>Decorated jewelry box</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jewelry_box_descr">
		<text>A small box full of woman jewelry. It seems quite valuable but Zoners generally don't wear jewelry, except for bloodsucker teeth, so it's not likely to fetch a good price.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] valuable</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_book1">
		<text>Mechanics manual</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_book1_descr">
		<text>Manual of mechanical engineering. Some people read such books to expand their expertise and learn more about the facilities and factories in the Zone. Low sale value.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+2%)</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_book2">
		<text>Engineering manual</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_book2_descr">
		<text>Manual of industrial engineering. Some people read such books to expand their expertise and learn more about the facilities and factories in the Zone. Low sale value.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+2%)</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_drugnotes">
		<text>Drug distribution notes</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_drugnotes_descr">
		<text>This notebook describes various drug deals in detail. Specific nicknames, locations and time of meets. Some deals are executed through equipment exchanges and others are paid in large amounts of rubles. When browsing the pages, it becomes clear that Freedom is the main distributor of natural drugs such as marijuana. Bandits are producers and distributors of the more powerful (and dangerous) synthetic drugs like salicylic acid and cocaine. Apparently, every faction in the Zone takes part in these deals. In particular, Monolith seems to be taking in large amounts drugs in exchange for more expensive types of ammunition and equipment.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] personal belongings\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] valuable\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+2%)</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_picture_woman">
		<text>Picture of a woman</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_picture_woman_descr">
		<text>A small picture of a beautiful woman with blond hair. The name at the bottom of the picture has been crossed out. Wrapped in plastic.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] personal belongings\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+1%)</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_porn2">
		<text>Ukrainian MAXIM</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_porn2_descr">
		<text>Glossy spreads with beautiful Slavic girls, featuring Joanna Krupa as the star of the month. A popular find among Zoners who need a psychological escape on a daily basis. The poster with Joanna has been removed.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+2%)</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_boots">
		<text>Leather boots</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_boots_descr">
		<text>Everyone is aware of the importance of good gear. An extra pair of boots can prove extremely useful and may be the object of envy of other stalkers since it is such a rarity.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] personal belongings\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] outfit repairs (+4%)</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_batteries_dead_empty">
		<text>Old batteries (emptied)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_batteries_dead_empty_descr">
		<text>Only one out of ten batteries found in the Zone still carry some juice. These, however, are completely drained and because of that do not have any value whatsoever.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] technological item\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] UPD charge: %c[0,204,0,51] none\n
		%c[0,204,0,51] • %c[0,140,140,140] depleted</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_batteries_empty">
		<text>Batteries (emptied)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_batteries_empty_descr">
		<text>These batteries have been completely drained of whatever energy they once had. Their only value is the amount of metal they are made of.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] technological item\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] UPD charge: %c[0,204,0,51] none\n
		%c[0,204,0,51] • %c[0,140,140,140] depleted</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_batteries_ccell_empty">
		<text>Military battery unit (emptied)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_batteries_ccell_empty_descr">
		<text>An empty military battery unit. If full they are very valuable and in high demand due to the relative scarcity of batteries in the Zone. However, now that the juice has run out they constitute a backpack burden.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] technological item\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] UPD charge: %c[0,204,0,51] none\n
		%c[0,204,0,51] • %c[0,140,140,140] depleted</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_flashlight_broken">
		<text>Broken flashlight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_flashlight_broken_descr">
		<text>The handle is broken and even duct tape wouldn't be able to keep the batteries in place. This is no longer of any value.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] technological item\n
		%c[0,204,0,51] • %c[0,140,140,140] broken beyond repair\n
		%c[0,204,0,51] • %c[0,140,140,140] unusable</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_underwear">
		<text>Soaked underwear</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_underwear_descr">
		<text>An extra pair of socks, a shirt and pants could substantially increase your comfort. Unfortunately, this set is completely soaked. There is little chance any stalker will pay for this garbage. Although they might seem worthless, the material the underwear is made of can be used in armor and weapon maintenance.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] personal belongings\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] outfit repairs, weapon maintenance (+3%)</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_spareparts">
		<text>Weapon spare parts</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_spareparts_descr">
		<text>Spare parts for what looks to be an AKM assault rifle. The wooden parts are not in a very good condition, and the same can be said of metal elements. Only novices would be interested in buying them. However, it seems that they may be useful for equipment repairs. Certain Zoners replace some parts when finding a new weapon out in the open in order to avoid being hunted for stealing from someone's stash.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] military item\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] outfit repairs, weapon maintenance (+10%)</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_beadspread">
		<text>Bed spread</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_beadspread_descr">
		<text>Luxury item in the Zone. It gives you extra 10 percent chance of a good night's sleep. Since there are only a few beds in safehouses in the Zone, having a sleeping bag and a bed spread may prove essential if you don't want to hit the wall in most inappropriate of circumstances. Bed spreads are included in the equipment of some military units.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] outfit repairs (+3%)</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_walkie">
		<text>Walkie talkie</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_walkie_descr">
		<text>The display is dead and there is a constant hiss from the speaker indicating that this is of no use. Has what appears to be mutant teeth marks on it.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] technological item\n
		%c[0,204,0,51] • %c[0,140,140,140] broken beyond repair\n
		%c[0,204,0,51] • %c[0,140,140,140] unusable</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_cards">
		<text>Deck of cards</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cards_descr">
		<text>It is important to divert your mind from suffering in this hellhole and focus on other, more pleasant things. Playing cards is a popular pastime, but a deck of cards can also be used for sorting special trades. The cover depicts the proud architectural design of the Moscow Metro.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mili_maps">
		<text>Military maps</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mili_maps_descr">
		<text>Maps showing the location of military camps around the Zone. Each PDA comes with these maps installed, so this item is of little use to anyone.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] military item\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+3%)</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_headlamp">
		<text>Old head lamp</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_headlamp_descr">
		<text>Although few dare to explore the Zone during the night, there are circumstances where a head lamp is crucial. And another source of light won't hurt, because you never know when you'll have to move from place to place. Unfortunately, this particular unit has long seen its working days and can now only serve as a source of cheap spare parts.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] technological item\n
		%c[0,204,0,51] • %c[0,140,140,140] broken beyond repair\n
		%c[0,204,0,51] • %c[0,140,140,140] unusable</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mirror">
		<text>Telescopic mirror</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mirror_descr">
		<text>Small mirror mounted on a telescopic iron tube. A handy item used by fighters versed in the arts of urban combat as it allows to peek around corners without getting shot.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] military item</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_hammer">
		<text>Old hammer (reusable)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hammer_descr">
		<text>Hammer with a wooden handle and an iron head. A common sight in industrial areas of the Zone. Despite its heavy weight, it's often carried in backpack due to its versatility.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] outfit repairs, weapon maintenance (+3%)\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] unlimited usages</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_tarpaulin">
		<text>Camouflaged tarpaulin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_tarpaulin_descr">
		<text>
		A tarpaulin (or hootch) is a large sheet of strong, flexible, water-resistant or waterproof material, often cloth such as canvas or polyester coated with urethane, or made of plastics such as polyethylene. It has reinforced grommets at the corners and along the sides to form attachment points for rope, allowing them to be tied down or suspended. Serves many purposes, but is mainly used to create small and simple tent-like hideouts. Trading value is low due to easily found alternatives.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] military item\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] outfit repairs, weapon maintenance (+5%)
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_synthrope">
		<text>2 synthetic ropes</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_synthrope_descr">
		<text>
		Synthetic ropes are commonly found in military warehouses. But for some reason few military stalkers actually carry them. A good rope serves many purposes, especially in a place like the Zone. Many stalkers can put this to good use, which generates a rather high trading value. Each is about 5 meters long.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] outfit repairs (+4%)
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_cutlery">
		<text>Field cutlery</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cutlery_descr">
		<text>
		A spoon, a knife and a fork made of heavy steel. A robust and reasonably light cutlery set, ideal for backpacking and field exploration. The cutlery is held together by a copper cord. If cleaned properly and derusted, it would be safe to use.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] weapon cleaning and lubrication (+2%)
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_radio">
		<text>Small radio</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_radio_descr">
		<text>
		Music is a good way to calm your nerves. But with a broken antenna this radio is of little use. Moisture and dirt have also damaged this item.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] technological item\n
		%c[0,204,0,51] • %c[0,140,140,140] broken beyond repair\n
		%c[0,204,0,51] • %c[0,140,140,140] unusable
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_radio2">
		<text>Broken radio</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_radio2_descr">
		<text>
		A small radio in a poor condition. Dirty and damaged by moisture. The interior seems to be in quite a bad shape as the radio rattles when moved around. No to little value.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] technological item\n
		%c[0,204,0,51] • %c[0,140,140,140] broken beyond repair\n
		%c[0,204,0,51] • %c[0,140,140,140] unusable
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_broken_detector">
		<text>Broken detector</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_broken_detector_descr">
		<text>
		A broken Bear detector. The screen is smashed and the interior seems to be in quite a bad shape. Some of the electronic parts inside are still safe. They can be reused for repair purposes, or perhaps even in crafting.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] technological item\n
		%c[0,204,0,51] • %c[0,140,140,140] broken beyond repair\n
		%c[0,204,0,51] • %c[0,140,140,140] unusable
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_gloves">
		<text>Leather gloves</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gloves_descr">
		<text>
		A pair of leather gloves. Feel and smell good as if they are bought recently. When the weather gets cold, it's important to keep your hands warm and ready.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] valuable
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] outfit repairs (+4%)
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_hand_watch">
		<text>Hand watch</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hand_watch_descr">
		<text>
		An old, classic Soviet "raketa3" watch. Looks like it's still in a good shape. It's not surprising that many stalkers prefer mechanical watches over PDAs for usual time checking. Giving the fact that those watches are reliable and durable even at the worst situations, they come in handy where PDAs fail due to strong electromagnetic waves coming from emissions or nearby anomaly fields. However, some simply wear them as a style accessory.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] personal belongings\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] technological item\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] valuable
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_ball_hammer">
		<text>Ball-peen hammer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ball_hammer_descr">
		<text>
		Also known as a machinist's hammer. Ball-peen hammer is a type of peening hammer used in metalworking. Despite being old and rusty, you can never go wrong with having one for small repair jobs.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+3%)\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_duct_tape">
		<text>Duct tape</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_duct_tape_descr">
		<text>
		Duct tape is commonly used in situations that require a strong, flexible, and very sticky tape. An easy and temporary solution for quick repair jobs. This type also has a long-lasting adhesive and resistance to weathering.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] outfit repairs, weapon maintenance (+3%)
		</text>
	</string>
		

	
<!-- Base -->	
	<string id="st_jar">
		<text>Plastic jar</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jar_descr">
		<text>
		A tiny plastic jar. Such jars are always handy for keeping small items safe, especially medicines. It protects the contents from moisture and ensures the moisture content of the product remains the same.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] basic material\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_e_syringe">
		<text>Empty syringe</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_e_syringe_descr">
		<text>A 12mL medical syringe with a lousy plunger. Seems like it has been used quite frequently. With a drug-making kit and proper knowledge, this syringe can come in handy for the creation of various types of medicines.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] basic material\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_ammo_bad">
		<text>Bad ammo</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_bad_descr">
		<text>
		Even with good supplies, it’s not uncommon to end up with one or more cartridges of what might be considered as “bad” ammunition. Unlucky stalkers might find themselves in very bad situations when their weapons jam at critical moments due to bad cartridges. On the contrary, this ammo can be reused for the creation of better variants. That's why some stalkers prefer to keep them around.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] basic material\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_rope">
		<text>Rope</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_rope_descr">
		<text>
		A good rope serves many purposes, especially in a place like the Zone. Many stalkers can put it to good use, which generates a rather high trading value. About 10-meters long.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] basic material\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] outfit repairs (+3%)
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_paper">
		<text>Paper sheets</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_paper_descr">
		<text>
		Torn sheets of silk coated paper. Even in a place like the Zone, it can be used for all kind of things. The cheapest way for packaging food or cleaning dirt.\n \n
		%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item\n
		%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] basic material\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] outfit repairs, weapon maintenance (+1%)
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_basic_textolite">
		<text>Textolite base</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_basic_textolite_descr">
		<text>
		Layered plastic based on fabric of fibers and polymeric binder (bakelite, polyester resin, epoxy resin). With proper skill it can be great help in repairing.\n \n
		%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] basic material\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] outfit repairs, weapon maintenance (+2%)
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_textile_patch_b">
		<text>Cloth sheet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_textile_patch_b_descr">
		<text>
		Simple cloth sheet, commonly used both to patch clothing and spread oils and cleaning solvents onto firearm mechanisms. Can be applied by any needle or glue.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] basic material\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] outfit repairs, weapon maintenance (+3%)
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_textile_patch_m">
		<text>Textile sheet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_textile_patch_m_descr">
		<text>
		Sheet of military-grade textile that can be used for field repairs of clothing and light armor. Valued for its relatively low price and high versatility, this material is commonly used by the Zoners. Medium-grade sewing equipment and advanced glue required for use. It can also be used to improve spread of liquids during weapon maintenance.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] basic material\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] outfit repairs, weapon maintenance (+4%)
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_textile_patch_e">
		<text>Reinforced textile sheet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_textile_patch_e_descr">
		<text>
		Thick textile patch reinforced with kevlar padding. Can be used to repair medium and heavy armors. Large enough to cover multiple damaged areas. High quality sewing kits and adhesives are required to make use of it. Its alternative usage is weapon lubrication and cleaning - due to increased hardness it's able reach even less accessible areas of firearm parts.\n \n
		%c[0,200,200,200]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,100,100,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] basic material\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] outfit repairs, weapon maintenance (+6%)
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_basic_capacitors">
		<text>A pack of capacitors</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_basic_capacitors_descr">
		<text>
		Electric capacitors can store electricity. The simplest capacitor consists of two metal plates and a dielectric between them. It is a main component is most of electrical devices due to its important job in rectifying alternative current, storing electrical energy and bypassing noise. They are quite rare in the Zone, but they are very useful.\n \n
		%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] basic material\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_basic_transistors">
		<text>A box of transistors</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_basic_transistors_descr">
		<text>
		A box of high-quality BJT transistors. A transistor consists of three Semiconductor parts (base, emitter, collector) that serve together to generate, convert and amplify electrical oscillations. The ultimate dream of electronics engineers, if such a miracle will bring to the Area.\n \n
		%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] basic material\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_basic_copper">
		<text>Copper wire</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_basic_copper_descr">
		<text>
		Electrotechnical copper wire is used practically in all devices, devices, apparatuses, installations, machines where the production, transmission or use of electric energy occurs. In its pure form it is rare, but if necessary it can be easily extracted from common old radios, walkie-talkies and other electronics.\n \n
		%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] basic material\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_basic_wood">
		<text>Wooden parts</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_basic_wood_descr">
		<text>
		Pieces of wide-grained, light cedar wood. Mostly used for outdoor projects such as furniture, decks and tools. White it's not that useful in a place like the Zone, it could be used in crafting.\n \n
		%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] basic material\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_basic_scrap">
		<text>Metallic scrap</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_basic_scrap_descr">
		<text>
		Handful of metal bolts, screws, bits and pieces of equipment. A variety of many different types and grades of steel and aluminum alloys. Could be used to aid in repairing gear in the field, or perhaps even in crafting.\n \n
		%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] basic material\n
		%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for: %c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+2%)
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_basic_glass">
		<text>Glass pieces</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_basic_glass_descr">
		<text>
		%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] basic material\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="basic_ceramic">
		<text>Ceramic base</text>
	</string>
	<string id="basic_ceramic_descr">
		<text>
		%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] basic material\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_basic_leather">
		<text>Leather roll</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_basic_leather_descr">
		<text>
		%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] basic material\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_basic_plastic">
		<text>Plastic film</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_basic_plastic_descr">
		<text>A small pack made of low density polyethylene film. These thin plastic membranes are used to separate areas or volumes, hold items and act as barriers. Plastic films are used in a wide variety of applications. Despite being partly torn, polyethylene's characteristics makes it a great solution for packaging and isolating, especially for food and medicines.\n \n
		%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] basic material\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_basic_rubber">
		<text>Rubber</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_basic_rubber_descr">
		<text>
		%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] basic material\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
</string_table>
