<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features">
		<text>Features</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_azazel_mode">
		<text>Azazel mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_azazel_mode_text">
		<text>
			%c[0,250,250,250]Azazel mode%c[0,170,170,170] allows you to continue playing as another character after death.\n
			\n%c[0,56,209,115]Information%c[0,170,170,170]
			\nIn Azazel mode death is not the end - upon the demise of your character you will posses the body of a random stalker who was previously controlled by the AI.\n
			\nShould you have companions at the time of your death, they will be given priority and you will continue playing as one of them instead.\n
			\nThis mode can only be enabled from the character creation screen.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_ironman_mode">
		<text>Ironman mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_ironman_mode_text">
		<text>
			%c[0,250,250,250]Ironman mode%c[0,170,170,170] adds an indirect layer of difficulty to gameplay, whereby all of your saved games for a character are deleted upon their death.\n
			\n%c[0,56,209,115]Information%c[0,170,170,170]
			\nShould Azazel mode be enabled at the same time you will be allowed to continue playing as whoever you switched to, but saves made as your deceased character will be deleted as per usual.\n
			\nWhen playing with this mode enabled all of the saves you make will be uniquely tagged as an ironman by the way, as such it is impossible for unrelated saves to be deleted by mistake.\n
			\nThis mode can only be enabled from the character creation screen.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_story_mode">
		<text>Story mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_story_mode_text">
		<text>
			%c[0,250,250,250]Story mode%c[0,170,170,170] enables a non-linear story based on the events of S.T.A.L.K.E.R. Shadow of Chernobyl.\n
			\n%c[0,56,209,115]Information%c[0,170,170,170]
			\nWith this mode enabled you start the game with the 'Mysteries of the Zone' storyline, and the tasks of disabling both the Brain Scorcher and the Miracle Machine.\n
			\nTo begin the story you will need to find an important individual hiding somewhere within the Zone, who after a brief dialogue will provide you with multiple tasks which can be completed in any order.\n
			\nThis mode can only be enabled from the character creation screen.\n
			\n%c[0,56,209,115]Availability%c[0,170,170,170]
			\n• Clear Sky\n• Duty\n• Ecologist\n• Freedom\n• Loner\n• Mercenary
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_survival_mode">
		<text>Survival mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_survival_mode_text">
		<text>
			%c[0,250,250,250]Survival mode%c[0,170,170,170] turns the Zone into a hunting ground - where you are the prey.\n
			\n%c[0,56,209,115]Information%c[0,170,170,170]
			\nWith this mode enabled all spawns are replaced with zombified stalkers and mutants, who will slowly stumble towards your location in an attempt to kill you.\n
			\nFeaturing a more prominent role are zombies themselves, the last devolution of zombified stalkers who have lost the ability to operate mechanical devices such as firearms.\n
			\nOnly a few traders and stalker squads can be found, meaning you will have to survive off of what you can scavenge in the world.\n
			\nThis mode can only be enabled from the character creation screen.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_campfire_mode">
		<text>Campfire mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_campfire_mode_text">
		<text>
			%c[0,250,250,250]Campfire save mode%c[0,170,170,170] prevents you from saving your progress the usual way. You can only save on nearby campfires.\n
			\n%c[0,56,209,115]Information%c[0,170,170,170]
			\nTo save your progress on a nearby campfire, you need a %c[0,250,250,250]Firestarter set%c[0,170,170,170] or a %c[0,250,250,250]Box of matches%c[0,170,170,170]
			\nApproach a nearby campfire until you see a message appearing on the HUD about it, then use one of the mentioned items to save your progress.
			\nYou can save your progress normally without campfires in underground levels.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_agony_mode">
		<text>Agony mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_agony_mode_text">
		<text>
			%c[0,250,250,250]Agony mode%c[0,170,170,170] adds another layer of difficulty by preventing you from saving your progress if some critical conditions are met.\n
			\n%c[0,56,209,115]Information%c[0,170,170,170]
			\n%c[0,56,209,115] You can't save your progress in Agony mode if you're:
			\n%c[200,200,200,50]• %c[0,150,150,150]Injured
			\n%c[200,200,200,50]• %c[0,150,150,150]Bleeding
			\n%c[200,200,200,50]• %c[0,150,150,150]Irradiated
			\n%c[200,200,200,50]• %c[0,150,150,150]In combat with enemies
			\n%c[200,200,200,50]• %c[0,150,150,150]Under circumstances of an emission or psi-storm
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_timer_mode">
		<text>Timer mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_timer_mode_text">
		<text>
			%c[0,250,250,250]In Timer mode%c[0,170,170,170], you can save your game every specific amount of time. 
			\nOnce you save your game, you cannot make another save once again until the timer is over.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_companions">
		<text>Companions</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_companions_text">
		<text>
			%c[0,250,250,250]Companions%c[0,170,170,170] are stalkers who can be recruited to your side, similar to followers and familiars in other games.\n
			\n%c[0,56,209,115]Information%c[0,170,170,170]
			\nWith the Zone being as dangerous as it is, most other stalkers can be found exploring in small groups, usually in size of around 3 to 4 individuals.\n
			\nThis feature allows you to do the same, as by talking to the leader of one of these groups you may be able to convince them to explore the Zone together with you.\n
			\nThe only requirements are that the squad's leader must have friendly relations with you, that his rank be no more than a single tier above yours, and that you haven't too many stalkers already following you.\n
			\nIn very special cases, characters such as Fanatic may be used as companions to help complete certain tasks, having their own unique set of requirements, and not counting towards your squad limit.\n
			\nInformation about your companions can be viewed in the Relations tab of the PDA, where you can also issue them orders as a group or individually, as well as change their behaviours.\n
			\nThis can also be done through key bindings, which can be set via the Controls options menu.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_guide">
		<text>Guide</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_guide_text">
		<text>
			The %c[0,250,250,250]Guide%c[0,170,170,170] is a resource to help teach you about the game and its contents.\n
			\n%c[0,56,209,115]Information%c[0,170,170,170]
			\nThis feature was added at much request by players to help explain features and gameplay mechanics, as well as to add a more visual representation of your progression.\n
			\nArticles are sorted by category, with all tutorial-esque and important content being unlocked right from creating your own character.\n
			\nWhen you unlock an article its name and category are displayed in the message, allowing you to find the content with relative ease.\n
			\n%c[0,56,209,115]Disclaimer%c[0,170,170,170]
			\nFor the first time since S.T.A.L.K.E.R.: Shadow of Chernobyl a serious attempt is being made at reintroducing a complete in-game user guide to all available content.\n
			\nAlthough this feature is mostly complete in function it is still in an early work-in-progress stage, and as such only a small percentage of articles have been written.\n
			\nBecause of the magnitude of such a task there is much more yet to be added, with many missing and incomplete categories, and the interactive unlock system not yet being fully integrated.\n
			\nBy introducing new articles with further updates and patches the guide will eventually be completed but it will take quite some time.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_hud">
		<text>HUD</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_hud_text">
		<text>
			The %c[0,250,250,250]HUD%c[0,170,170,170] shows you indicators regarding various important states regarding your health and equipment.\n
			\n%c[0,56,209,115]Information%c[0,170,170,170]
			\n%c[0,250,250,250]State%c[0,170,170,170] indicators represent the current negative state of your health and equipment. A gray indicator is shown if the related state is slightly bad, while yellow is concerning. Orange and red determine critical states.
			\n%c[0,250,250,250]Danger%c[0,170,170,170] indicators are shown when you enter a dangerous zone, which have a direct effect on your health or equipment. The worse the color, the more damage you constantly get.
			\n%c[0,250,250,250]Boosting%c[0,170,170,170] indicators are shown as long as you're under effects of a booster item. They are either protection or healing indicators. Once the effects of the used item fade away, the related indicators will disappear afterwards.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_map_spots">
		<text>Map spots</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_map_spots_text">
		<text>
			%c[0,250,250,250]Map spots%c[0,170,170,170] are icons which appear on the map to highlight points of particular interest.\n
			\n%c[0,56,209,115]Information%c[0,170,170,170]
			\nMany locations and entities have map spots associated with them, making it easier to read the map at a glance without having to worry about remembering tons of information.\n
			\nYou are able to create your own custom map spots by double-clicking on the map and entering a name to be displayed when hovered over - these can be renamed or removed later by right-clicking them and selecting the appropriate context option.\n
			\n%c[0,56,209,115]Toggles%c[0,170,170,170]
			\nAnomalous areas, important objects (traders, technicians, beds, etc.), stashes, and task waypoints can be toggled within the PDA by pressing the aptly named buttons at the top of the map tab.\n
			\nRegardless of these settings, those which are attributed to stalkers and other moving objects are always visible on your minimap - as there is no guarantee they will remain stationary and in a single location.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_rank">
		<text>Rank</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_rank_text">
		<text>
			%c[0,250,250,250]Rank%c[0,170,170,170] is a score system based on what a stalker has accomplished in the Zone.\n
			\n%c[0,56,209,115]Information%c[0,170,170,170]
			\nActions which you perform throughout your playthrough are recorded and each grant a varying number of points depending on the action in question.\n
			\nAs you accumulate more and more points your rank will gradually change as you pass through every milestone, with each requiring an additional 1,000 points on top of the requirements of its predecessor.\n
			\nMost of these actions are logged in the statistics tab of the PDA, which also contains an in-game leaderboard that keeps track of the current top-100 highest ranking stalkers.\n
			\n%c[0,56,209,115]Ranks%c[0,170,170,170]
			\n• Rookie: 0\n• Trainee: 1,000\n• Experienced: 3,000\n• Professional: 6,000\n• Veteran: 10,000\n• Expert: 15,000\n• Master: 21,000\n• Legend: 28,000
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_reputation">
		<text>Reputation</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_reputation_text">
		<text>
			%c[0,250,250,250]Reputation%c[0,170,170,170] is a representation of how a stalker interacts with others.\n
			\n%c[0,56,209,115]Information%c[0,170,170,170]
			\nReputation is similar to rank but differs in that it isn't quite so linear - being able to both increase and decrease - and that it is based on your interactions with other stalkers rather than the environment.\n
			\nThe easiest ways to increase reputation are by completing tasks, providing first-aid, and killing your faction's enemies, whilst inversely the easiest ways to lose it are by cancelling or failing tasks, and killing neutral or friendly stalkers.\n
			\nIt should be noted that whilst it is used by some features, reputation is largely immersion-focused and should not be confused with goodwill.\n
			\n%c[0,56,209,115]Reputations%c[0,170,170,170]
			\n• Terrible: -2,000\n• Dreary: -1,500\n• Awful: -1,000\n• Bad: -500\n• Neutral: 0\n• Good: 500\n• Great: 1,000\n• Brilliant: 1,500\n• Excellent: 2,000
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_stashes">
		<text>Stashes</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_stashes_text">
		<text>
			%c[0,250,250,250]Stashes%c[0,170,170,170] are items stored by stalkers in often well-hidden locations.\n
			\n%c[0,56,209,115]Information%c[0,170,170,170]
			\nMost stalkers in the Zone store spare ammunition, food, and medicines in containers, backpacks, and other hidden objects with the intent to retrieve them later.\n
			\nFrequently the information as to their whereabouts dies with the stalker who hid them, resulting in numerous stashes full of unused items strewing the landscape waiting to be discovered at any time.\n
			\nInformation brokers and traders often give coordinates to stashes as a bonus payment for those who have done good work for them, whereas those in a tight pinch might try to use their own personal stashes to barter for their survival.\n
			\nYou can create your own stashes by right-clicking and selecting the appropriate option on any backpack in your inventory.\n
			\nStashes which you create are never looted by other stalkers, so your items will always be safe.\n
			\n%c[0,56,209,115]Identification%c[0,170,170,170]
			\nThe type and/or status of a stash can be easily determined by looking at its icon on the map or by hovering your mouse cursor over it.\n
			\n• Green: Untouched\n• Purple: Partially looted\n• Yellow: Player-owned\n• Red: Unique
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_awr">
		<text>AWR</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_awr_text">
		<text>
			%c[0,250,250,250]Advanced Weapon Repair (AWR)%c[0,170,170,170] allows the player to repair his/her weapon at a mechanic's workshop\vice.
			\n \n%c[0,56,209,115]Information%c[0,170,170,170]
			\nInstead of paying mechanics to repair your weapons, you can use their vices to do the repair yourself as long as you have the required gears.
			\nThe repair procedure is affected by the overall quality of the weapon (new, worn, rusty) and its current condition. Moreover, the terms 0-65, 0-75 and 0-85 determine the weapon status for each of the quality types:
			\n• 0-65% for rusty weapons.
			\n• 0-75% for worn weapons.
			\n• 0-85% for new weapons.
			\n \n%c[0,56,166,209]Required items and toolsc%c[0,170,170,170]
			\n• Replacement parts (should be suitable for your weapons. You can get them by disassembling similar weapon types using the %c[0,250,250,250]Multitool%c[0,170,170,170])
			\n• Weapon repair kit
			\n• Weapon modification kits
			\n \n%c[0,56,166,209]Repair and upgrade procedurec%c[0,170,170,170]
			\nReplacing parts when repairing weapons with a low state occurs in a certain sequence:
			\n• At condition 0-20/0-25/0-30% - Replacement of barrel
			\n• At condition 20-35/25-45/30-55% - Replacement of trigger (shock-trigger mechanism)
			\n• At condition 35-45/45-60/55-70% - Replacement of breech head
			\n• At condition 45-55/60-70/70-80% - Replacement of gas tube
			\n• At condition 55-65/70-75/80-85% - Replacement of breech block
			\n \n%c[0,209,209,56]Steps:%c[0,170,170,170]
			\n1• Disassemble your weapon at a mechanic's vice.
			\n2• Select a %c[0,250,250,250]weapon repair kit%c[0,170,170,170] to replace the weapon barrel with another barrel of the same caliber, this can be also done by using a %c[0,250,250,250]weapon upgrade kit%c[0,170,170,170] in a condition from 20-65%/25-75%/30-85%. Double click on the kit to apply the repair procedure.
			\n3• Select a %c[0,250,250,250]Weapon modification kit%c[0,170,170,170] to replace the rest of parts in the list. 
			\n4• Click on the image of the part that is being currently replaced (the part selected for the replacement that is available for replacement is indicated by a green light). Attempting to replace one part spends one charge of the %c[0,250,250,250]Weapon modification kit%c[0,170,170,170] (keep in mind that a modification kit can be used 3 times)
			\n5• In case the replacement is successful, this procedure is repeated for all parts in the specified order
			\n6• In case the part has been damaged, try again if there is a repair kit and any more weapon parts.
			\n7• All replaced parts are retained until the condition of the weapon is lowered. In this case, to improve the quality, the parts will need to be replaced anew.
			\n8• When all five parts have been replaced, the quality of the weapon will be changed to the corresponding one. On that note, if at least one of the replaced items has been worn out, the quality of the weapon will be changed to "worn", even if other weapon parts are replaced with new ones.
		</text>
	</string>
	
</string_table>